Guide to the Robert A. Hill Collection, 1890-2014 RL.10993
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research (RE), 1889-2012 and undated; 10
  - General, 1
    - Philipps, J.E.T. and W.E.B Dubois Correspondence, 1921-1932 (Box RE190)
    - Philipps, J.E.T. and A.P. Wadsworth Correspondence, 1945-1950 (Box RE190)
    - Mahdism, 1918-2002, undated; 3 folders (Box RE191)
      Includes correspondence from Secretary of State for the colonies; and articles on Mahdism.
    - Mohammedanism, 1916-2002 (Box RE191)
    - Lord Alfred Milner, Articles, 1958-2001, undated (Box RE191)
    - Arabia, 1983-2002, undated (Box RE191)
      Includes article on Pan-Arabism and British Policy.
    - Philipps, J.E.T., Memorandums and Writings, 1917, undated (Box RE191)
    - Islam, 1922-2002, undated (Box RE191)
      Includes articles by Lothrop Stoddard; Wilfrid Scawen Blunt; and Philip Catzeflis.
    - Young Turks, 2002, undated; 2 folders (Box RE191)
      Includes articles by Mohammad Sadiq; historical abstracts; and appendices.
    - The Beat Magazine, Vol. 21, No. 6, 2002 (Box RE193)
    - Centre for Middle Eastern and Islamic Studies, 2003 (Box RE193)
    - Ahmad, Muhammad, 2002 (Box RE193)
    - Buchan, John, 2002 (Box RE193)
    - Wingate, Francis Reginald, 1989 (Box RE193)
      Includes Donald C. Coventry's manuscript on the career of Wingate.
    - Blacks in the American Revolution, 2001-2005 (Box RE193)
    - Worldview, 1998, 2003 (Box RE193)
      von Herder, Johann Gottfried
    - Black Soldiers in the American Revolution, 2005 (Box RE193)
      Attucks, Crispus
    - Freemasonry, 1997, 2000, 2004 (Box RE193)
    - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 2005, undated (Box RE193)
    - Redding, Grover Cleveland, 1915-1922, 1980, undated (Box RE193)
      Includes correspondence and clippings from Chicago Defender.
    - In Battle for Peace, the Story of my 83rd Birthday, 1952 (Box RE193)
      DuBois, W.E.B.
    - Autobiography of DuBois, W.E.B., 1968 (Box RE193)
    - Duse Mohamed vs. Wilfred Scawen Blunt, Plagiarism, 1910-1911 (Box RE193)
    - Sir Basil Thomson, Home, 2006 (Box RE193)
    - Cuban Gods and Their African Sources, 2005; 3 folders (Box RE193)
      In Spanish
    - Black Man's Burden Review, 1920 Mar 25 (Box RE193)
    - Using Uganda's archives, 2000 (Box RE193)
      Barrett-Gaines, Kathryn
    - C.L.R. James, Archive, 1997 (Box RE193)
    - Pan-Africa and Anti-white, 1921 Oct (Box RE193)
      Philipps, J.E.T.
    - Soldiers to New Negroes, 2007 (Box RE193)
      Williams, Chad
    - Malcolm X, 1990 (Box RE193)
      Includes newspaper clippings and memorial pamphlet.
    - African Americans in South Africa, 1998 (Box RE193)
    - African/African American Literature, 1998-2000 (Box RE193)
    - Race and Women, 2001 (Box RE193)
      Delany, Martin Robison; and Cathe John.
    - Nettleford, Rex, 1999, 2010 Feb 16 (Box RE193)
    - Using Uganda's Archives, 2006, 2010 (Box RE193)
    - Society for the Friendless, 1926 Jul (Box RE193)
    - Rodney, Walter, 2007 (Box RE193)
    - International Ethiopian Rescue and Relief Association, 1919, 1945, 1954 (Box RE193)
      Includes constitution; by-laws; and articles of incorporation.
    - Garvey, Articles, 1925-1928, 1970, undated (Box RE193)
    - Thomas Clegg, Ancestry, 1825 (Box RE193)
    - Sir James Arthur, Biography, undated (Box RE193)
    - Garvey and UNIA, Vol. IV, 1983 (Box RE193)
      Hill, Robert A.
    - Garvey and UNIA, Vol. X, 1997 (Box RE193)
    - Garvey, Character Background, 1921, 1925, undated; 2 folders (Box RE193)
    - Obeah in Jamaica, 2008 (Box RE193)
    - Dark Star Rising, Occultism Dissertation, 1997-1998; 3 folders (Box RE193)
      Verter, Bradford J.M.
    - Briggs, Cyril V., 1919, undated (Box RE194)
    - Clegg, African Cotton, 1857 (Box RE194)
    - Barnes, J.E., Case Documents, 1906; 5 folders (Box RE194)
    - Abyssinia, 1927 (Box RE194)
    - Christianity, 1935-2008 (Box RE194)
      Includes clippings from The New York Times.
    - Ethiopian Princes, Articles, 1905-1907 (Box RE194)
    - Zionism, 2008 (Box RE194)
    - Jazz, Reggae Articles, 2014 (Box RE194)
    - Chicago Abyssinian Parade, 1920 Jun 21 (Box RE194)
    - Religious history and Cults, Research, 2004-2010 (Box RE194)
    - Seventh Emmanuel's Brethren, Certificate of Membership, 1959 (Box RE194)
    - Kingston, Jamaica - Activities of Claudius, Henry V., 1959 (Box RE194)
    - Rastafari Brethren Correspondence with British Government, 1960 (Box RE194)
    - Rastafari Articles: Roots of the Rastas, 1978 Apr 9 (Box RE194)
    - The New Creation International Peacemakers Association, undated (Box RE194)
    - Twelve Plagues of Jamaica, undated (Box RE194)
    - The Age of Projects, Clark Library Exhibition, 2004 (Box RE194)
    - Religion and Rastafari Articles, 2006, undated (Box RE194)
    - Bible and Christianity Articles, 2004-2008 (Box RE194)
    - Queen of Sheba Exhibition, 2004-2005 (Box RE194)
    - Ethiopian Archbishop, Article, 2006 (Box RE194)
    - Written Records of Philipps Meetings, 1937, 1944 (Box RE195)
      Box 195 contents include J.E.T. Philipps materials.
    - Philipps, Writing, 1940 (Box RE195)
    - Uganda, 1917-1920 (Box RE195)
    - Philipps, Correspondence and Memorandums, 1917-1918 (Box RE195)
      Includes correspondence with District Commissioners Office in Kabale.
    - Philipps and Kigezi, Correspondence, 1919 (Box RE195)
    - Mohammedanism, 1918 (Box RE195)
    - Pan-Islam and Swahili, 1918 (Box RE195)
    - Okpaku vs. Esquire Magazine, 1972 (Box RE195)
    - Ottoman Empire, 1917, 2003 (Box RE195)
    - Garvey, Marcus, 1976 (Box RE195)
    - Philipps and Wilson, Correspondence, 1917 (Box RE195)
    - Pan Islam and Philipps, Writing, 1917-1919 (Box RE195)
    - Egypt Treaty and Letters, 1916-1919 (Box RE195)
    - World News, 2001 (Box RE195)
    - African American Articles, 1915 (Box RE195)
    - Bridgmen Convention Papers, 1921 (Box RE195)
    - Colonies, 1921 (Box RE195)
    - Communism, 1982 (Box RE195)
    - Caribbean, 1987 (Box RE195)
    - Nile, Correspondence, 1923, 1929, 1949 (Box RE196)
      Research materials in Box RE196 are related to J.E.T. Phillips.
    - Pan-Turanian Movement, 1919 (Box RE196)
    - Africa, 1919 (Box RE196)
      Major Stigand; African World.
    - Egypt and the Middle East, 2002 (Box RE196)
    - Report and Letters, 1915 (Box RE196)
    - World War I, 1915-2003 (Box RE196)
    - Student Debates, 2003 (Box RE196)
    - Pan-Islam and Africa, 1917-1918; 2 folders (Box RE196)
    - Pan-Asiatic Movement, 1934 (Box RE196)
    - Pan-Islam and India, 1923 (Box RE196)
    - Islam and the Caliphate, 1919 (Box RE196)
    - Bazley, Sir Thomas, undated (Box RE196)
    - Rwanda, 1921-1923 (Box RE196)
    - Philipps - International Union for the Protection of Nature, 1956-1960 (Box RE197)
    - Crawford, Kirwan, Philipps - Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box RE197)
    - Medieval theories About the Nile, Paper, 1949 (Box RE197)
      Crawford, O.G.S.
    - J.E.T. Philipps, Correspondence from the Royal Geographic Society, 1920-1949 (Box RE197)
    - Annotated Subjects, undated; 2 folders (Box RE197)
    - The Beat - Reggae Magazine, 2002 (Box RE197)
    - Religion and Adaptation in Rural Jamaica, Dissertation, 1978; 2 folders (Box RE197)
    - Anti-witchcraft Cults in Asank, 1981 (Box RE197)
    - Garvey Dread or the Conjury of Marcus Garvey, 2003 (Box RE197)
    - Resurrection, 2008 (Box RE197)
      Knohl, Israel
    - Other Powers: Taylor's Principle and the Power of Banality, undated (Box RE197)
    - Witchcraft, Sorcery, and Religion, undated (Box RE197)
    - Rastafarianism, undated (Box RE197)
    - Brown, Edward, undated (Box RE197)
    - Garvey and Psychic Science, 1982, undated (Box RE197)
      Includes handwritten notes; clippings; and H.G. Wells.
    - Isaac Rose, Interviews, 1975-1986, undated (Box RE197)
    - Footnotes, undated (Box RE197)
    - Memorial and Diary of Jesse Miller, 1950 (Box RE197)
    - March Garvey, Sr., 1895-1920, undated (Box RE197)
    - Interviews, undated; 2 folders (Box RE197)
      Chippie; Monroe, Albert; Laughlin House; Brown, R.A.; Gordon, Aaron; Bell, Clarence; and Saunders.
    - Technologies, Masonic Writings, undated (Box RE197)
    - Caribbean Kinship, Race, Witchcraft, 2006-2008 (Box RE197)
      Putnam, Laura
    - The Occult, 2005-2007 (Box RE197)
    - Witchcraft, 1936-2008 (Box RE197)
      Includes articles and clippings on witchcraft by Florence Bernault; Michael Bailey; and from The Times.
    - Obeah, 2005-2008 (Box RE197)
    - Jamaican Labor Migration, 1988 (Box RE197)
    - Death and the Invisible Powers, 1993 (Box RE197)
      Bockie, Simon
    - Cuba, Articles, undated (Box RE197)
      Includes articles by Franklin Knight; Alejandro de la Fuente; and Aline Helg.
    - Challoughliczilczise, W.S.J. and Black Nationalism on the Great Plains, undated (Box RE198)
    - Challoughliczilczise, W.S.J., J.S. Wyrewizard, US Department of State Records, 1924-1955 (Box RE198)
    - W.S.J. Challonzlluzallizise, 1920-1922, undated (Box RE198)
    - Challoughlczilczise, Texas and Oklahoma Investigations, 1920 (Box RE198)
      Includes facsimiles of correspondence; and reports.
    - Abyssinian Priest, Historical Newspapers, 1905-1940 (Box RE198)
    - Imposters, Huckleberry Finn, 2006 (Box RE198)
    - Joseph Emanuel Blayechattai, Autobiography and Ancestry, 1905-1940 (Box RE198)
    - The Pen of an African, 1922 (Box RE198)
      Blayechattai, J.E., Dr.
    - Hidden Mystery of Ethiopia, 1928-1929 (Box RE198)
      Blayechattai, J.E., Prince
    - Princes of Abyssinia, Chicago Riot, 1920 Jun (Box RE198)
    - Fallen Angels, 2007-2008, undated (Box RE198)
      Chancy, Myriam J.A.
    - European Imposters, 2016 (Box RE198)
    - Conzos F. Checzzli, records, death records, 2017 (Box RE198)
    - Rev. Father C.F. Checzzli, 1908, 1921 (Box RE198)
    - An Abyssinian Prince, 1892 (Box RE198)
    - Americanizing Abyssinia, 1933 Aug (Box RE198)
    - Yohannes of Ethiopia, 2008 (Box RE198)
      Zewditu I
    - Shervington, Prince, 1924-1925 (Box RE198)
      Includes articles in the Pittsburgh Courier and 19th century British newspapers.
    - Imposters and African Princes, 1914, 1925, 2007, undated (Box RE198)
    - Relationality, From Attachment to Intersubjectivity, 2000 (Box RE198)
      Mitchell, Stephen A.
    - Jamaican Princes, 1816, 1907, 1975 (Box RE198)
    - Rev. Prince Kaba Rega, 1917, 1944 (Box RE198)
    - Correspondence Regarding Prince Challoughlozilozise, 1923 (Box RE198)
    - Prince of Ethiopia, Sabbath Recorder, 1922 Aug 7 (Box RE198)
    - Selassie, Haile, 2014 (Box RE198)
      Includes photocopies of photographs
    - Limb, Peter, Biographical Annotations, 2009 (Box RE198)
      C. S. Mabaso; Z.P. Ramailane; and Richard Thema.
    - Ilanga Lase Natal, 1919, undated (Box RE198)
    - Msiman, Richard W., undated (Box RE198)
    - Life and Times of Lij Iyasu, Program, 2009 Nov (Box RE198)
    - Chicago Raid, 1912 Nov (Box RE198)
      de Laurence, I.W., Dr.
    - Interview Notes, 1996 (Box RE198)
      Includes materials from Polly Hill, British social anthropologist of West Africa.
    - Reverend James Walker Hood Eason, 2005 (Box RE198)
    - Slavery, 1970, 1990, 1992 (Box RE198)
    - African Anecdotes, The Living Age, 1925 Apr (Box RE198)
    - Thomas Clegg, Letter, undated (Box RE198)
    - The Crusader, Introduction, undated (Box RE198)
    - Ainsworth and Dickson, Correspondence, 1919 (Box RE198)
      Kenya National Archives
    - Padmore and Locke, Correspondence, 1936 Dec (Box RE198)
      James, C.L.R.
    - Challoughliczilczise, W.S.J., J.S. Wyxewizard, US Department of State Records, undated (Box RE198)
      Hogsbjerg, Christian
    - Smitherman, Andrew J., 1914, 2016 (Box RE198)
    - Tulsa Race Riot, 2011, 2016, undated (Box RE198)
    - Africans and Religion, 2013-2014 (Box RE198)
      Bedasse, Monique
    - Blacks, Migration to Nova Scotia, 1787-1817, 2012 (Box RE198)
    - W.E.C. to Robert R. Morton, Correspondence, 1918 Mar 18 (Box RE198)
      Tuskegee Institute
    - UNIA, World Race War, End of White Rule, 1921 Aug 2 (Box RE198)
      Clipping from New York Tribune
    - Joseph Chamberlain Papers, 1895-1924; 3 folders (Box RE198)
      Colonial office papers and correspondence; JC 29.
    - Colonies: Sierra Leone, 1876-2005 (Box RE198)
    - Antebellum America, 2007 (Box RE198)
    - Interrelations Between History and Philosophy of Science, undated (Box RE198)
    - Migration, 2007 (Box RE198)
    - Slavery, 2006 (Box RE198)
    - The Adventurer, 1919-1934 (Box RE198)
      Garvey, Marcus
    - Benefit Benevolence, 1918-1929 (Box RE198)
    - Garvey, speeches, 1919-1935; 3 folders (Box RE198)
    - Harlem Mecca of the New Negro, ePrint (book), 1925 (Box RE192)
      Survey Graphic
    - Harlem on my Mind (book), 1968 (Box RE192)
      Shoener, Allon
    - African American Institutional Study Final Report (book), 1991 (Box RE192)
      Smithsonian Institution
    - Playing the Race Card (book), 2001 (Box RE192)
      Williams, Linda
    - Black Art: A Cultural History (book), 2002 (Box RE192)
      Powell, Richard J.
    - Swinging the Machine (book), 2003 (Box RE192)
      Dinerstein, Joel
    - Real Black: Adventures in Racial Sincerity (book), 2005 (Box RE192)
      Jackson, John L.
    - Bedassse, Monique, 2005 (Box RE192)
    - Death and Power in the World of Atlantic Slavery (book), 2008 (Box RE192)
      Brown, Vincent
    - The Price of Liberty, 2002; 3 folders (Box RE199)
      Clegg, Claude III.
    - Afro-American, Newspaper, 1920-1922 (Box RE199)
    - Savannah Tribune, 1920 Jun 9-1922 (Box RE199)
    - The Broad Ax, 1920-1922 (Box RE199)
    - Philadelphia Tribune, 1920 Jan-1922 Dec (Box RE199)
    - New York Age, 1920 Jan-1922 Dec (Box RE199)
    - Chicago Defender, 1920 Jan-1922 Dec (Box RE199)
    - Richmond Planet, 1920 Jan-1922 Dec (Box RE199)
    - Cleveland Gazette, 1920-1922 (Box RE199)
    - Messenger, 1920 (Box RE199)
    - The Production of India, 1998 Aug; 8 folders (Box RE199)
    - List of Black Newspapers, 1921 Jun (Box RE199)
    - Negro World, 1921-1925 (Box RE199)
    - Baltimore Afro-American, 1923-1924 (Box RE199)
    - New York Age, 1923 Jan 27-1925 Aug 29 (Box RE199)
    - Philadelphia Tribune, 1924 Mar 22-1925 Mar 28 (Box RE199)
    - Messenger, 1923 May-1924 Nov (Box RE199)
    - Messenger, 1922 Dec-1925 May (Box RE199)
    - Chicago Defender, 1922 Nov 4-1925 Dec 5 (Box RE199)
    - Pittsburgh Courier, 1922 Mar 8-1925 Aug 22 (Box RE199)
    - The Crisis, 1923 Jan-1925 Nov (Box RE199)
    - California Eagle, 1923 Aug 17-1925 Jun 12 (Box RE199)
    - Savannah Tribune, 1922 Dec 7-1925 Nov 19 (Box RE199)
    - Chicago Broad Ax, 1923 Mar 10-1925 Mar 21 (Box RE199)
    - Norfolk Journal and Guide, 1922 Dec 23-1925 Nov 28 (Box RE199)
    - The Richmond Planet, 1923 Mar 10-1924 Feb 23 (Box RE199)
    - Cleveland Gazette, 1922 Dec 16-1924 Dec 20 (Box RE199)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, 1925, 1923-1933 (Box RE199)
    - Clippings, 1925, 1924-1975 (Box RE199)
    - Leo Wiener, materials, 2001 Oct 30, 1923 Aug 10 (Box RE199)
    - Locke Papers, 1923 Dec 12 (Box RE199)
    - Calling up the Empire, 1990; 7 folders (Box RE199)
    - Harlem Renaissance, 2007, undated (Box RE199)
    - Harlem Beat, 1994 (Box RE199)
      Includes fax from Barbara Myers.
    - Confessions of a Taxi Driver, 1935, 1994 (Box RE199)
      Harlem Hacker
    - Garden Gods: A Story of Love, Intrigue, and Adventure in African Jungles, 1933-1934 (Box RE199)
      George Schuyler articles, as published in the Pittsburgh Courier.
    - Harlem Renaissance, Basketball, 1919-1994 (Box RE199)
    - Obeah, Conference, 2003 (Box RE199)
    - Huiswood, Otto Edward, 1958, 1982 (Box RE199)
    - Rhetoric of Empire, 1993 (Box RE199)
    - Scholes, T.E.S., 1982 (Box RE199)
    - Communist Movement at a Crossroads, 1923 (Box RE199)
      In German.
    - Stock Yards Labor Council, 1919 (Box RE199)
    - Fort-Whiteman, Lovett, 1917, 1923, 1982 (Box RE199)
      Includes correspondence with the F.B.I.
    - Archival Sources to the History of the Netherlands, 1980 Jan (Box RE199)
      Antilles Van Soest
    - Garvey, Surveillance, 1920 (Box RE199)
    - Irish Americans, 1986 (Box RE199)
      de Valera, Eamon
    - Central Executive Committee, Communist Party of America, undated (Box RE199)
    - Ingersoll, Robert Green, 1932 (Box RE199)
    - Gitlow, Katherine, 1921 (Box RE199)
    - Briggs, Cyril, 1958, undated (Box RE199)
    - Katayama, Sen. Joseph, 1983 (Box RE199)
    - Paul Crouch, Surveillance, 1928 (Box RE199)
    - New Masses, Publication, 1926-1927 (Box RE199)
    - Radical Black Publications and the Espionage Act, 1919-1920 (Box RE199)
    - Ford, James William, 1932, undated (Box RE199)
    - Lovestone, Jay, undated (Box RE199)
    - West Indian Immigration, 1980 (Box RE199)
    - Black Moses and his Dream of the Promised Land, 1921 Mar (Box RE199)
    - History of the Library, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - Mimesis, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - Anti-colonialism, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - Derrida and Archives, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - Opportunity: A Journal of Negro Life, 1923-1924 (Box RE200)
    - Guillaume, Paul, 1924, 1984 (Box RE200)
    - Africa: Journal of the International African Institute, 1952 (Box RE200)
    - Barnes Foundation Archives, undated (Box RE200)
    - Barnes Correspondence, Documents, and Photographs, 1922-1924 (Box RE200)
    - Barnes and Locke, Correspondence, 1924 (Box RE200)
    - Barnes Foundation, Papers, Correspondence, and Documents, 1924-1929; 2 folders (Box RE200)
      Includes materials on the NAACP.
    - Inventing Futurism: The Art and Politics of Artificial Optimism, 2008 (Box RE200)
      Poggi, Christine
    - Michael Fabre, Articles, 1975-2009 (Box RE200)
    - Prince Kojo, 1924 (Box RE200)
    - Problem with Evil and Crime, 2008 (Box RE200)
    - Articles on Europe and Britain, 1991-2006 (Box RE200)
    - The Folk Culture of the Slaves, undated (Box RE200)
    - Inequalities in Bangladesh, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - Keeping Watch Over the Dead, 2007 (Box RE200)
      Cotter, Holland
    - The Gleaner, Articles, 1899-1923 (Box RE200)
    - Negro Newspaper Articles, 1920-1924 (Box RE200)
    - Self-Made Man, 2006-2007, undated (Box RE200)
      Catano, James
    - French Art, 1923-2009 (Box RE200)
    - Black Man's Art, 1926-2009 (Box RE200)
    - The New Yorker, Books, 2008 (Box RE200)
    - New York Passenger Lists, 2009 (Box RE200)
    - Existentialism, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - Autopoiesis, 1928, undated (Box RE200)
    - Clegg, Thomas, 2005, 2009 (Box RE200)
    - Baker, Josephine, 2006-2009 (Box RE200)
      Includes announcements for contemporary exhibitions.
    - Gnosis Archive, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - African American Newspapers, 1959 (Box RE200)
      Includes letters from the Old World.
    - The Red Hot Jazz Archive, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - The William Blake Archive, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - Cultural Politics, 2007, undated (Box RE200)
    - Chicago Defender, Articles, 1922 (Box RE200)
    - Book Decoration and Portraits, 1925 (Box RE200)
    - Chinese Pyramids, undated (Box RE200)
    - World War, Egypt, 1923 (Box RE200)
    - Roland Hayes, Article, 1923 (Box RE200)
      Locke, Alain
    - Cultural Transactions: Nature, Self, Society, 2007 (Box RE200)
    - Thomas Hodgkin, Biography, 2008 (Box RE200)
    - The Preservation of Research Data in a Postmodern Culture, 2005 (Box RE200)
    - Memory and Remembering the Past, 2007 (Box RE200)
      Levine, David
    - Witchcraft, Magic, Black Magic, undated (Box RE200)
    - Garvey, Rastafari Prophecy, 2008 (Box RE200)
    - Garvey, UNIA Reports, 1920-1924 (Box RE200)
    - W.E.B DuBois, Documentary Script, 1993 (Box RE200)
    - African Americans and Anti-colonialism, 1937-1957, undated (Box RE200)
    - Africa Irredenta, 1925-1939 (Box RE200)
      Philosophy and Opinions of Marcus Garvey and African response.
    - Italian Fascism, 2000 (Box RE200)
    - England and the British Empire, Articles, undated (Box RE200)
    - Garvey, Pamphlets, Letters, Articles, and Speeches, 1919-1935; 2 folders (Box RE200)
    - Garvey, Speeches, 1919-1935; 3 folders (Box RE200)
    - Electronic Records, 2008, undated (Box RE201)
      Collection contains electronic records that may need to be reformatted. Access copies of electronic records must be accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services for access.
    - Walter Rodney, Articles, 1980 (Box RE202)
    - Blacks, Cubans, and the Siege of Miami and the Failure of Tantrum Politics Articles, 1980 (Box RE202)
    - Jamaican Group Photographs, undated (Box RE202)
    - Jamaican Watchman, Articles, 1869 (Box RE202)
    - Haiti, Photograph in The Guardian Newspaper International, 2008 (Box RE202)
    - African Art and Music, Articles, 1990, 2007 (Box RE202)
    - Hill, Quote in UCLA African Studies Program, Article, 1991 (Box RE202)
    - General Sir Reginald Wingate Papers, Sudan Collection, Durham University, 1895, 1911, 1914, undated (Box RE202)
    - Henry Wilson, Fox Railway Report, 1920 (Box RE202)
    - HRH, The Prince of Ethiopia, Look! Listen!, Detroit, 1922 (Box RE202)
    - Public Records Office Correspondence, 1916-1920; 4 folders (Box RE202)
      Contents include PRO holdings on: British Policy in Africa; German East Africa; Tanganyika; and Dr. Mohamed and the Islamic Society.
    - Book Reviews, with Hill's Notes, 1985, 2003-2004, 2007-2008 (Box RE202)
      General Sir Reginald Wingate Papers, Sudan Collection, Durham University
    - McCarthyism in the 20th Century, Article, 2003 (Box RE202)
    - Voodoo, Article, 2003 (Box RE202)
  - Photographs and Facsimiles, 3
    The Photographs and Facsimiles subseries includes 8x10, 4x7, and 5x9 inch photographs as well as 3x5 inch negatives collected by Robert Hill for research and production purposes for the UNIA volumes. Production elements include facsimiles on photographic paper, portraits and photographs of groups arranged by volume, if possible, and unarranged negatives. Research photographs include unidentified portraits and group photographs as well as negatives.
    - Chief August Mokhatle, Liberia, African Nationalism, and Africa facsimiles and subject Files, 1917-1981, undated; 110 folders (Box RE90)
    - Vol. 8 photos, 1995-2000, undated (Box RE144)
    - Vol. 8 photo negatives, undated (Box RE144)
    - Vol. 3 frontispiece, undated (Box RE144)
    - Dunkley, H. (Henry Archibald), undated (Box RE144)
    - McGuire, George Alexander, undated (Box RE144)
    - Vol. 2 photographs, 1921-2002, undated (Box RE144)
    - Vol. 1 photographs, 1988-1994, undated (Box RE144)
    - Vol. 1 frontispiece, 1920-1987, undated (Box RE144)
    - UNIA Divisions and Harlem Map Vol. VII, undated (Box RE144)
    - Vol. 10 frontispiece, 1996 (Box RE144)
    - Vol. II fascimiles, Garvey II, undated (Box RE144)
    - Vol. 3 photographs, 1922-1994 (Box RE144)
    - Vol. 11, undated (Box RE144)
    - Fascimile for Vol. 12, undated (Box RE144)
    - Caribbean Series Vol. 11 photographs, undated (Box RE144)
    - Photographsto be used in Vol. 12 and 13, 1920-1923, undated (Box RE144)
    - UNIA Convention Parade - negatives, 1914, undated (Box RE144)
    - UNIA Convention Parade, 1922, undated (Box RE144)
    - Graphics collection negatives, undated (Box RE144)
    - Pinnacle negatives, undated (Box RE144)
    - Pinnacle, undated (Box RE144)
    - Town Hok River photographnegatives, undated (Box RE144)
    - Town Hok River, undated (Box RE144)
    - Nelson, D.J. - thesis, University of Birmingham, undated (Box RE144)
    - Negatives Robert Hill Talk at WR Bookshop, undated (Box RE144)
    - Marcus Garvey in Parade with Hat, 1922 (Box RE144)
    - Marcus Garvey in Parade with Hat - negative, 1922 (Box RE144)
    - Bishop Henry Turner, Rev. Henry Parks, Rev. James Dwane, Rev. Flipper - Ethiopian and AME Church merging, undated (Box RE144)